04/03/2023, 19:45 SuNnY BiByAn



ABOUT

Seeking a beginner role to enhance and explore my technical knowledge gained at Deenbandhu Chhotu Ram University of Science and Technology, University Murthal Sonipat in the last three years. I hold a B.Tech degree from South Point Institute of Technology and Management Campus

EDUCATION

2019-08 - 2022-07

B.Tech: Electronics And Communications EngineeringSouth Point Institute of Technology And Management - Sonipat,
Haryana 131001

2013-08 - 2016-06

Diploma: Electronics And Communications Engineering Govt.Polytechnic Sonipat - Sonipat, Haryana 131001

2012-03 - 2013-03

10th

Govt. Model Sanskarti Sr. Sec. School - Ganaur, Sonipat, Haryana 131101

SUNNY

Software Engineer



Ganaur, Sonipat, Haryana PinCode-131101



+91-7876286522



sunnykumar6121997@gmail.com



github.com/HunnYCodes



linkedin.com/in/sunny-bibyan-84a26b232

SKILL'S

HTML CSS

JavaScript

Jquery

React.js

EXPERIENCE

2022-03 - 2022-06

Internship

Wonderful Services & Technology Solutions, Gurgaon, Haryana

2017-03 - 2019-03

Repair Engineer

Vivo Mobile India Private Limited, Greater Noida, Uttar Pradesh

PROJECT'S

Contect_Form-1/HTML/CSS
Project